Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive, 1966-2000 (bulk 1970-1995) MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series III: Production Files, 145412
  - Subseries A: Mabou Mines productions, 145415
    - Warrior Ant script, undated; 153844 (Box 139, Folder 2379)
    - Dressed Like an Egg Sydney Opera House: light plots, 1979-1980 (Folder 7)
    - Oversize page prints - Dressed Like and Egg and unidentified project, undated; 153845 (Box 139, Folder 2380)
    - Adelaide Arts Theatre: light plots and floor plan, 1979 (Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: Mabou Mines-related productions, 145413
    Oversize production files from Mabou Mines-related productions.
    - Voyage of the Beagle poster: preservance Theatre, Douglas, AK, 1986-1987; 145414 (Box 22, Folder 936)
    - Poster - Philip Glass performance, 11/15/72, 1972; 153843 (Box 139, Folder 2381)
  - Subseries D: Mabou Mines film productions, 151979
    - Dead End Kids credits galleys, 1986; 152160 (Box 139, Folder 2375)
    - Dead End Kids audio recording cue sheets, undated; 151980 (Box 139, Folder 2376)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Photographs, 145406
  - Subseries A: Production photographs, 145407
    Oversize documentary photographs of Mabou Mines productions.
    - Dressed Like an Egg Richard Landry; prints, 1977; 145411 (Box 31, Folder 1221)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice prints; Japan, undated; 145410 (Box 31, Folder 1222)
    - The Saint and the Football Players prints, undated; 145409 (Box 31, Folder 1223)
    - Company photos print, undated; 145408 (Box 31, Folder 1224)
- OVERSIZE Series VIII: Touring Files, 145372
  - Subseries A: Touring Files by Production, 145378
    Oversize touring files: mostly light plots, maps, and posters.
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Apr 1981; UC Santa Cruz posters, 145405 (Box 44, Folder 1619)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice / Hajj Aug 1984; Japan tour maps, 145404 (Box 44, Folder 1620)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1-4, 1985; Kent State University maps, 1984; 145403 (Box 44, Folder 1621)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 17-18, 1985; University of Tennessee, Chattanooga maps, 145402 (Box 44, Folder 1622)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 3, 1985; Poughkeepsie, NY track sheets, 145401 (Box 44, Folder 1623)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 7-10, 1985; University of Hartford light plot, maps, brochures, 145400 (Box 44, Folder 1624)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 11, 1986; University of Vermont, Burlington light plot, track sheets, venue brochures, 145399 (Box 44, Folder 1625)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 14, 1986; Williams College, Williamstown, MA track sheets, 145398 (Box 44, Folder 1626)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC light plot, track sheets, 145397 (Box 44, Folder 1627)
    - Cold Harbor Sep-Oct 1986; University of Iowa, Iowa City track sheets, 145396 (Box 44, Folder 1628)
    - Cold Harbor [Sep-Oct?] 1986; Soutwest Missouri State University, Springfield, MO light plots, track sheets, 145395 (Box 44, Folder 1629)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Vallodolid, Spain theater plans, 145394 (Box 44, Folder 1630)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1987; Port of History Museum, Philadelphia light plot, 145393 (Box 44, Folder 1631)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 9, 10, 1987; St. Louis, MO track sheets, 145392 (Box 44, Folder 1632)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Stockton State College, NJ light plots, 145391 (Folder 1)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Owensboro, KY light plot, 145390 (Folder 15)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 17-18, 1985; University of Tennessee, Chattanooga light plots, 145389 (Folder 14)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Catamount, St. Johnsbury, VT light plot, 145388 (Folder 13)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; University of Massachusetts at Amherst light plot, 145387 (Folder 12)
    - Cold Harbor Feb-Mar 1986; Theatrical Outfit, Atlanta, GA ground plan/light plot, 145386 (Box map case, Folder 1642)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC map, 145385 (Folder 3)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 7, 1986; University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign light plot, track sheets, 145384 (Folder 2)
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; UC Davis light plot/ground plan, track sheets, 145383 (Folder 10)
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; Humboldt State University, Arcata, CA light plots, ground plans, 145382 (Folder 9)
    - Cold Harbor Jan 1987; Theatre Artaud, San Francisco, CA light plot, track sheets, 145381 (Folder 8)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain light plot, ground plan, track sheets, 145380 (Folder 7)
    - Company Sep 22-25, 1987; University of Texas at Austin light plot, track sheets, 145379 (Folder 6)
  - Subseries D: Organizations and Festivals, 145373
    Oversize files relating to national and international theater organizations and festivals.
    - American Center in Paris ground plan, 1990; 145377 (Box 44, Folder 1633)
    - New York International Festival of the Arts press, poster, 1988; 145376 (Box 44, Folder 1634)
    - Sundance Institute poster, 1991; 145375 (Box 44, Folder 1635)
    - Yellow Springs Institute poster, 1990; 145374 (Box 44, Folder 1636)
    - Beckett Festival light plot, undated (Folder 2)
- OVERSIZE Series X: Press, 145358
  - Subseries A: General Press, 145369
    Oversize press items about the company generally, and about awards and nominations.
    - Vogue Jul 1972 "New Physical Theater" by Barbara Rose, 145371 (Box 49, Folder 2033)
    - Obie Awards May 26, 1987, 145370 (Box 49, Folder 2034)
    - LA Weekly May 11, 1984 (Vol 6 No 24) "Women in Film" issue, 152161 (Box 139, Folder 2377)
    - "Works" Wexner Center performing arts catalog, 1990; 152162 (Box 139, Folder 2378)
  - Subseries B: Company Members & Associates, 145365
    Oversize press items about company members.
    - Akalaitis various Oct-Dec 1989 re: "The Seasons", 145368 (Box 49, Folder 2035)
    - Breuer Village Voice May 19, 1987 "American Theater's Wild Man", 145367 (Box 49, Folder 2036)
    - Breuer Bomb Summer 1996, 145366 (Box 49, Folder 2037)
  - Subseries C: Productions, 145359
    Oversize press items about Mabou Mines and related productions.
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Interview Jun 1988, 145364 (Box 49, Folder 2038)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Artforum Sep 1984, 145363 (Box 49, Folder 2039)
    - Lear New York Times Magazine Sep 10, 1989, 145362 (Box 49, Folder 2040)
    - Lear Lower Manhattan Cultural Council Downtown Arts Activities Calendar Jan 1990, 145361 (Box 49, Folder 2041)
    - Warrior Ant New York Times Magazine Nov 9, 1986; Oct 16, 1988, 1986, 1988; 145360 (Box 49, Folder 2042)
- OVERSIZE Series XII: Financial Files, Grants, and Development, 152166
  - Mabou Mines Development Foundation general accounting journal, 1973-1979; 152167 (Box 140)
  - Quotidian Foundation / Mabou Mines Development Foundation financial journal, 1979-1982; 152168 (Box 140)
  - Film Journal, 1982-1983; 152169 (Box 140)
- Unprocessed Accretion (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68, Box 69, Box 70, Box 71, Box 72, Box 73, Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Box 77, Box 78, Box 79, Box 80, Box 81, Box 82, Box 83, Box 84, Box 85, Box 86, Box 87, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 91, Box 92, Box 93, Box 94, Box 95, Box 96, Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 100, Box 101)